<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Inventing Games</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Inventing Games</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Describing The Game</title>
      <link>/posts/gamedescription/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gamedescription/</guid>
      <description>This article will be continuously updated to reflect changes made in the game during implementation and to be aligned with other articles.  
I don&amp;rsquo;t make a goal to create a game that will be world-wide popular. Moreover, I realize that game creation alone is a really hard task and generally it is done by a game studio.
I don&amp;rsquo;t set a gameplay as a cornestone of this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Background</title>
      <link>/posts/gamebackground/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gamebackground/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Game’s Essentials</title>
      <link>/posts/gameessentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gameessentials/</guid>
      <description>In this set of articles I review basic concepts related to game development on JavaScript:
 Game Loop article describes what a game loop is and what it is used for. Game Loop in JavaScript article describes how the game loop is organized in JavaScript. Canvas article describes what a canvas is and how it is used.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Loop</title>
      <link>/posts/gameloop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gameloop/</guid>
      <description>Before I provide you with a definition of a Game Loop I would like to look at some corner concepts.
What is a Computer Program? What a strange question? Everyone knows the answer! I can agree with that statement, but do you really know what computer program is in essence? After ten years in software development and thousands lines of code I&amp;rsquo;m re-thinking this question.
 A computer program is a collection of instructions that perform a specific task when executed by a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Loop in JavaScript</title>
      <link>/posts/gameloopjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gameloopjs/</guid>
      <description>JS</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>